{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "8x^5", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^3√(2) * 2x^2√(2)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n4x^5√(4)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^6) * √(8x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "27x^3√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n9x√(x) * 3x^2\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n27x^3√(x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x^3) * √(9x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(6)/3", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(x) / x√(6x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(2)x√(1/6)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^5) / √(6x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2)/7", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^2√(2) / 7x^2\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1/7)√(2)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(2x^4) / √(49x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "44x^5√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n11x^2√(2x) * 2x^3√(2)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n22x^5√(4x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(242x^5) * √(8x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^5√(11)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2 * x^3√(11)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n2x^5√(11)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^4) * √(11x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^4√(6x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^2√(6) * 3x^2√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n3x^4√(6x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(6x^4) * √(9x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16√(6x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2√(2) * 8√(3x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n16√(6x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8) * √(192x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^2√(21)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n√(21x) * 7x√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n7x^2√(21)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(21x) * √(49x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3/10", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n3x^3 / 10x^3\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(3/10)√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^6) / √(100x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "54x^5", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n6x^2√(3) * 3x^3√(3)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n18x^5√(9)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(108x^4) * √(27x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x√(10x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n5√(5) * 2x√(2x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n10x√(10x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(125) * √(8x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11√(2x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n11 * √(2x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n11√(2x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(121) * √(2x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^5√(10)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n5x^2 * x^3√(10)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n5x^5√(10)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(25x^4) * √(10x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5x)/10", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^2√(5x) / 10x^2\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1/10)√(5x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(5x^5) / √(100x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "21x^3√(10x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n7x^3√(5) * 3√(2x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n21x^3√(10x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(245x^6) * √(18x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7x)/4", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^2√(7x) / 4x^2\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1/4)√(7x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^5) / √(16x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4√(70)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx√(10) * x^3√(7)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\nx^4√(70)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(10x^2) * √(7x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "55x^3", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n5x * 11x^2\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n55x^3√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(25x^2) * √(121x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "110x^2√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n5√(3x) * 22x√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n110x^2√(3)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(75x) * √(484x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "385x√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n11x√(5) * 7√(5x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n77x√(25x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(605x^2) * √(245x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x√(30x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2√(5) * x√(6x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n2x√(30x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(20) * √(6x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(5x)/3", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^3√(5) / 6√(x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1/3)x^3√(5(1/x))\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(20x^6) / √(36x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x√(10x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n10 * x√(10x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n10x√(10x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100) * √(10x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "77x^5", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n7x^2√(x) * 11x^2√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n77x^5√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x^5) * √(121x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12x^2√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n3x√(x) * 4x\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n12x^2√(x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^3) * √(16x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16x^5√(6x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n16x^3 * x^2√(6x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n16x^5√(6x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(256x^6) * √(6x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "22x^5√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(x) * 11x^3\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n22x^5√(x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^5) * √(121x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "30x^5√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^2√(15) * 10x^3√(3)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n10x^5√(45)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(15x^4) * √(300x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^3 / 2x√(x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1)x^2√(1(1/x))\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^6) / √(4x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(5x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2√(5) * 3√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n6√(5x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(20) * √(9x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^4√(10)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx√(10x) * 3x^2√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n3x^4√(10)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(10x^3) * √(9x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx√(5x) * 2x^2√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n2x^4√(5)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(5x^3) * √(4x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "22x^3√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^3 * 11√(3)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n22x^3√(3)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^6) * √(363)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "24x√(2x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n8√(3) * x√(6x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n8x√(18x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(192) * √(6x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2√(10)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(2) * √(5)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n2x^2√(10)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^4) * √(5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2√(33)/11", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(3) / √(11)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(2)x^2√(3/11)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(12x^4) / √(11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(6)/2", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n9x^2 / x^2√(6)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(9)√(1/6)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x^4) / √(6x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n3 * 4\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n12√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9) * √(16)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11x^4√(22)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n11x * x^3√(22)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n11x^4√(22)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(121x^2) * √(22x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^4√(10)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^2√(10) * 3x^2\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n3x^4√(10)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(10x^4) * √(9x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3√(7)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n√(7x) * 2x^2√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n2x^3√(7)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x) * √(4x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "36x^3√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x√(2x) * 9x^2√(2)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n18x^3√(4x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^3) * √(162x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "22x^2", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n11√(x) * 2x√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n22x^2√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(121x) * √(4x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16x^3√(6)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n8 * 2x^3√(6)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n16x^3√(6)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64) * √(24x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^2√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2√(3) * 3x^2\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n6x^2√(3)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(12) * √(9x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x√(6)/2", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n9x / √(6)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(9)x√(1/6)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x^2) / √(6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12x^2√(2x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n6√(2) * 2x^2√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n12x^2√(2x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(72) * √(4x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^2√(7x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n7√(x) * x^2√(7)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n7x^2√(7x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x) * √(7x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "28x^3√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(2x) * 7x√(2)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n14x^3√(4x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^5) * √(98x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11x^2√(10x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n11√(x) * x^2√(10)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n11x^2√(10x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(121x) * √(10x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n4x√(2x) / 4√(x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1)x√(2)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(32x^3) / √(16x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "40x^2", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n4 * 10x^2\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n40x^2√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(16) * √(100x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x/2", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n7x√(x) / 2√(x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(7/2)x√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x^3) / √(4x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2√(11x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x * x√(11x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n2x^2√(11x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^2) * √(11x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11x^3√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^3√(11) * √(11x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\nx^3√(121x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(11x^6) * √(11x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "48x^4√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n6x√(3) * 8x^3\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n48x^4√(3)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(108x^2) * √(64x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2√(11x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n3x√(x) * x√(11)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n3x^2√(11x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^3) * √(11x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^3√(6) / x^3√(2)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1)√(3)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(6x^6) / √(2x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "24x^2√(2x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n8√(x) * 3x^2√(2)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n24x^2√(2x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64x) * √(18x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(5x)/2", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n3x^2√(5) / 6√(x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1/2)x^2√(5(1/x))\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(45x^4) / √(36x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12x^3√(5x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(5x) * 6x\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n12x^3√(5x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(20x^5) * √(36x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^2√(3) * x^2√(5)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\nx^4√(15)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(3x^4) * √(5x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^3√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n5x^3 * 2√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n10x^3√(x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(25x^6) * √(4x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "40x√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n8 * 5x√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n40x√(x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64) * √(25x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5√(x)/7", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n5x^2√(x) / 7x^2\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(5/7)√(x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(25x^5) / √(49x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "128x^3", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n8x * 16x^2\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n128x^3√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64x^2) * √(256x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^4√(6x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(2) * x^2√(3x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n2x^4√(6x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^4) * √(3x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^3√(2x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n5x^3 * √(2x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n5x^3√(2x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(25x^6) * √(2x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^3√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n6x * x^2√(5)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n6x^3√(5)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36x^2) * √(5x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^2√(10)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx√(10x) * 9√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n9x^2√(10)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(10x^3) * √(81x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^3√(10x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx√(10) * 8x^2√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n8x^3√(10x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(10x^2) * √(64x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3√(66)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^3√(6) * √(11)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\nx^3√(66)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(6x^6) * √(11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x√(110x)/55", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n4x^2√(2x) / x√(55)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(4)x√(2/55x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(32x^5) / √(55x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^2√(10x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n√(5) * 10x^2√(2x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n10x^2√(10x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(5) * √(200x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^4√(6x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^3√(2) * x√(3x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\nx^4√(6x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(2x^6) * √(3x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n9 * x√(2)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n9x√(2)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81) * √(2x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2√(2x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx^2√(2x) * 3\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n3x^2√(2x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(2x^5) * √(9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "21x√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n3 * 7x√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n21x√(x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9) * √(49x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^4√(2x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(2x) * 3x^2\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n6x^4√(2x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^5) * √(9x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "18x^3√(2x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n9x√(x) * 2x^2√(2)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n18x^3√(2x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x^3) * √(8x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3√(77)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\nx√(11) * x^2√(7)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\nx^3√(77)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(11x^2) * √(7x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11x√(7x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n11 * x√(7x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n11x√(7x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(121) * √(7x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3√(35)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n√(7x) * x^2√(5x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\nx^3√(35)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x) * √(5x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2√(35)/35", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2√(x) / √(35x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(2)x^2√(1/35)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^5) / √(35x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3√(110)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n√(10x) * x^2√(11x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\nx^3√(110)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(10x) * √(11x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "22x^2√(15x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n11√(3) * 2x^2√(5x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n22x^2√(15x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(363) * √(20x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "42x^3√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n7x^2√(3x) * 2√(6x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n14x^3√(18)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(147x^5) * √(24x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^4√(6x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n8x√(x) * x^3√(6)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n8x^4√(6x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64x^3) * √(6x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(6)/3", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x√(2x) / x√(3x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(2)√(2/3)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^3) / √(3x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14x^2√(x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2 * 7√(x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n14x^2√(x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^4) * √(49x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12x^3√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n6x^2√(x) * 2√(2x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n12x^3√(2)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36x^5) * √(8x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(x)/9", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^3 / 9x^2√(x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(2/9)x√(1(1/x))\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^6) / √(81x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^3√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n5√(x) * x^2√(2x)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n5x^3√(2)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(25x) * √(2x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2x)/3", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2 / 3x√(2x)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(2/3)x√(1/2(1/x))\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^4) / √(18x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n3x^3 / 3x^2\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(1)x√(1)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^6) / √(9x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9√(5x)/20", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n9√(x) / 4√(5)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(9/4)√(1/5x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x) / √(80)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x√(2)/2", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n6x^3 / 2x^2√(2)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(3)x√(1/2)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36x^6) / √(8x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2√(3)/21", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n2x^2 / 7√(3)\nNow divide the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n(2/7)x^2√(1/3)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^4) / √(147)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^3√(6x)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both radicals.\n4x√(x) * x^2√(6)\nNow multiply the rational and irrational parts of both radicals\n4x^3√(6x)\nNow just simplify the radical and the result is the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(16x^3) * √(6x^4)", "type": "text"}
]}